http://www.keyevents.com/privacy-policy

Key Events Privacy PolicyLAST UPDATED: JUNE 11, 2018This Privacy Policy describes Key Events’ privacy practices as they relate to the collection, security, use and dissemination of personal information through our websites, applications and services (collectively, the “Services”), as well as the individuals’ rights regarding use, access and correction of their personal information. Key Events (or the “Company”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit our websites or applications (“Visitors”), individuals who use our services (“Customers”), and individuals who register to attend our events (“Attendees”). By accessing or using Company’s websites, applications or services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth herein.Key Events collects, processes, stores, discloses and disposes of Personal Information that you submit to us in accordance with applicable United States law, which may be less stringent than the laws of your country. Please note that the Personal Information you provide will be transferred to the United States, and to other countries where Company’s Services are provided on your behalf, for processing for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. You acknowledge and agree that we may collect, use and store your Personal Information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy, outside of your resident jurisdiction.If you have questions or complaints regarding Company’s Privacy Policy or associated practices, please contact us at registration@keyevents.com.1. What is covered by this Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy covers the information practices of websites and applications that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively referred to as “Company’s websites”). If a website or application does not link to this Privacy Policy, then it is not covered by Company’s Privacy Policy. Company’s websites may contain links to third party websites which are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Also, personal information of Attendees may be shared with, processed by and appear on websites or applications of Company’s Customers, business partners and vendors. In that case, the information practices and content of such websites or applications is governed by their respective privacy policies and not by this Privacy Policy. Additionally, if a Company’s website or application runs natively on a vendor platform, this Privacy Policy will apply to personal information in such website or application only when it links to this Privacy Policy. When a website or application of Company’s Customer runs natively on a vendor platform, the privacy policy of the Customer applies, and this Privacy Policy does not.2. Information collected“Personal information” means information that is received by Company by way of its Services and that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual. For example, Company collects personal contact information, such as your name, company name, title, address, phone number and email address, when individuals express an interest in obtaining information about Company’s Services, register on Company’s website, or register for an event or other Services. When registering for an event or purchasing Company’s Services, Company may also receive your financial and billing information, such as billing name, address and credit card number. Company may also receive additional information relating to lodging, transportation, disabilities, dietary restrictions and menu options. Also, if you apply for a job with the Company, we may require you to submit additional personal information as well as a resume or curriculum vitae. All of the foregoing information provided directly or indirectly by you are referred to as “Data.”As you navigate the Company’s websites, Company may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies (“Website Navigational Information”). Website Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Company’s websites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked).3. Use of information collectedCompany uses Data about its Visitors, Customers and Attendees to perform the services requested. For example, if you fill out a “Contact Me” Web form, the Company will use the Data provided to contact you about your interest in the Services. Company does not share, sell, rent, or trade your Data with third parties for their promotional purposes except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.Company uses Data about its Customers and Attendees to plan and host events, arrange for travel and lodging, and host online forums and social networks in which Attendees may participate. Company also uses such Data to populate online profiles for Attendees on other websites and applications of Company’s Customers and vendors in the provision of services to Customers and Attendees. In these situations, it is Company’s Customers who decide the purposes for which Attendee Data will be used. For additional information on how Attendee Data will be used and protected, please refer to the privacy policies of the Customers on whose behalf Attendees submitted their Data. Additionally, Company uses credit card information of Customers and Attendees to make and hold reservations and to collect payment from existing and prospective Customers and Attendees.Company may use Data about its Visitors, Customers and Attendees for administrative and marketing purposes. For example, Company may use information you provide to contact you to discuss your questions or interest in the Services and to send you information regarding the Company, its affiliates, and its partners, such as information about promotions, events and surveys.Company may also use Data about its Visitors, Customers and Attendees for business purposes such as data analysis and identifying usage trends; audits, security and fraud monitoring and prevention; developing new services and improving existing Services; determining the effectiveness of our promotions, events and Services; and operating and expanding our business activities. This may include the disclosure of Data and content of communications in order to comply with the law and to act in good faith to protect the rights or property of our business, employees, customers and vendors.Company also uses Website Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company’s websites and to provide customized information about the Company as more fully described below.4. Website Navigational InformationCookies, Web Beacons and IP AddressesCompany uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies to collect information as you navigate Company’s websites (“Website Navigational Information”). We and our partners use these cookies and similar technologies to analyze trends, administer Services and track users’ movements around our websites. This section describes the types of Web Site Navigational Information collected through Company’s websites and Services, and how it may be used.Cookies Company uses cookies to make interactions with our websites easy and meaningful. When you visit one of our websites, Company’s servers send a cookie to your computer. Unless you choose to identify yourself by filling out a Web form (such as a “Contact Me” form), you will remain anonymous to us. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features of Company’s websites or Services.Log Files, IP Addresses, URLs and Other DataLike most other websites, we may gather certain information automatically from your use of Company’s websites and Services. This information may be used to analyze overall trends, to help us improve our websites and Services, to track and aggregate non-personal information, and to provide the websites and Services. Company may also collect IP addresses from Customers when they log into the Services as part of Company’s security features.Social Media Features and Single Sign-onCompany’s websites may use social media features, such as the Facebook “like” button (“Social Media Features”). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the website and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on the website to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party social media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features.5. Public forumsCompany may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on its websites. Any personal information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums. Company is not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums.6. Sharing of information collectedCompany may share your Data with Company’s Customers, vendors and business partners. Those who receive your Data are expected to apply privacy and security protections consistent with this Privacy Policy. They are authorized to use your Data only for the purpose it was intended or as required by law. Unless otherwise dictated by law or agreement, Company is not responsible for improper use of your Data by its Customers, vendors or business partners; however, Company will take prompt remedial action in response to any reported or discovered misuse of your Data.VendorsCompany may share Data with its vendors so they can provide services on our and your behalf. We require our vendors to use and disclose personal information only as reasonably necessary to perform the services or to comply with applicable law. Company may also share Data with its vendors to ensure the quality of the Data provided by you.CustomersIf you are registering for an event or for Services through Company, Company may share Data about Attendees with Company’s Customers who are sponsoring or hosting you for the event or Services so Company can provide the services requested. Such Customers may receive Attendee Data directly from you or indirectly from Company. Company does not control their use of your Data, which will be in accordance with their own privacy policies.Business PartnersFrom time to time, Company may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. If you purchase or express interest in a jointly–offered product or service from or through one of our business partners, Company may share Data about its Customers collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our partners. Company does not control the business partners’ use of the Data, and their use of the Data will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may opt not to purchase or express interest in a jointly-offered product or service. If you choose to share your information with business partners, your information will be subject to the business partners’ respective privacy policies.Billing Company uses a third-party vendor to manage credit card processing which is not permitted to store, retain, or use billing information except for the purpose of credit card processing on Company’s behalf.Necessary DisclosureCompany may use or disclose information provided if required by law or if Company reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of Company or of its employees, customers and vendors, and/or to comply with judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. Company may also use or disclose personal information provided when necessary for the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business, assets or equity (including in the case of reorganization, dissolution or investment).7. International transfer of information collectedCompany primarily stores Data about its Visitors, Customers and Attendees in the United States. To facilitate Company’s global operations, however, Company may transfer and access such Data from around the world, including other countries in which Company, its Customers or its vendors do business. This Privacy Policy shall apply even if Company transfers such Data to other countries.8. Communications preferencesCompany offers Visitors, Customers and Attendees who provide contact information a means to choose how the Company uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the Company’s marketing emails.9. Consent to collection and modification of your informationYour decision to provide Data directly or indirectly to Company is voluntary. If you do not provide the Data requested, you may not be able to proceed with the activity or receive the benefit for which it is being requested. You can always unsubscribe or choose not to receive communications from us by following the specific instructions in the email you receive or by notifying us as provided below.If you provide any Data relating to another person, you represent that you have the authority and right to do so and permit us to use the Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Company may retain your Data for a period of time consistent with the purpose of collection and permitted use, consistent with Company’s data retention policies, and as required by applicable law. For instance, we may retain your information during the time in which you have an account to use our websites or Services and for a reasonable period of time afterward. We may also retain your information during the period of time needed for Company to pursue our legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.You may request to review, correct, delete or otherwise modify any of your Data that has been stored in Company’s websites and Services. If you registered for an account with Company, or with one of its Customers or vendors, you may be able to update your user settings, profile, organization’s settings and event registration information by logging into the applicable website or Service and editing your settings or information. Please contact your account representative or the customer service team if such functionality is not available in the applicable website or Service, or to update your billing information, discontinue your account, and/or request deletion of your Data. For other requests to access, correct, modify or delete your Data held by Company, please see the “Contacting Us” section below. Requests to access, change, or delete your Data will be addressed promptly, within a reasonable timeframe. If you are an employee or client of (or otherwise affiliated with) one of Company’s Customers, you should also contact that Customer for assistance in correcting or updating your information with them.10. Customer DataCompany’s Customers may electronically submit personal information to Company’s websites or Services for hosting and processing purposes (“Customer Data”). Company will only retain, access, process and distribute Customer Data as reasonably necessary to provide the services requested, perform the Customer agreements and comply with applicable law. Company acknowledges that you have the right to access and modify your personal information. If Data pertaining to you as an individual has been submitted to us by a Customer and you wish to exercise any rights you may have with respect to such Data, please inquire with our Customer directly. Since Company may have limited ability to access and modify Data provided by our Customers, if you wish to make your request directly to Company, please provide the name of Company’s Customer who submitted your Data. We will refer your request to that Customer and support them as needed in responding to your request within a reasonable timeframe.11. Information SecurityCompany uses appropriate technical and organizational measures designed to protect your Personal Information against loss or accidental, unlawful or unauthorized alteration, access, disclosure or use. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us immediately.12. ChildrenChildren are not eligible to use or make purchases of Company’s Services and we ask that anyone under the age of 13 not submit any Personal Information to us. Company does not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13.13. Changes to this Privacy PolicyCompany reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes to our Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting of the updated Policy on our website. Your continued use of our website or Services following posting of the updated Policy shall indicate your acknowledgment and agreement to be bound by the new Policy with respect to Personal Information provided both before and after the date on which it was posted.14. Governing lawThis Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms of Use and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the state of California, as further provided in the Terms of Use.15. Contacting usQuestions regarding this Privacy Policy or Company’s information practices should be directed to us at: registration@keyevents.com
Ready to Create Lasting Change? Contact us today.
Get Started!We put the power of our global network of strategic partners to work for you.The result?Global ReachNegotiating PowerFlawless ServiceWOW Experiences
Follow Us on Instagram!
COMFORT + JOY // Wishing you a season filled with
COMFORT + JOY // Wishing you a season filled with
COMFORT + JOY // Wishing you a season filled with
KEY INCLUSIVE HOLIDAY PARTY // The goal of any par
KEY INCLUSIVE HOLIDAY PARTY // The goal of any par
KEY INCLUSIVE HOLIDAY PARTY // The goal of any par
This error message is only visible to WordPress admins
News + ViewsGet our latest thinking on event strategy, design, industry trends and more.
SUBSCRIBE!
You have Successfully Subscribed!
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
